AI gives answers. Alpha Gym trains judgment.
Replay, decide, reveal, and review: the user stays responsible for the judgment.
The home page frames the app as a decision hall, not another generic dashboard.
Users practice on past snapshots without future leakage, then reveal the true outcome.
A fixed hover inspector keeps daily OHLC and indicators above the chart.
Fundamentals include valuation and quality signals instead of one long paragraph.
GPT is used for AI summaries, debate, judge scoring, and personalized coaching.
The coach critiques the submitted reasoning, not a canned template.
Live analysis uses the same workbench, then records entry price, time, side, and rationale.
The app separates live portfolio decisions from historical practice answers.
Codex built the full stack; GPT-5.6 powers the AI path through structured JSON.
GitHub: github.com/houyehh/FinDebate