Bull vs Bear Arena turns AI market analysis into blind judgment practice.
The product reverses the usual AI workflow: decide first, reveal judge scores later.
Ticker lookup validates symbols with yfinance and shows a 30-day price line.
Bull and Bear each produce three evidence-backed opening claims.
Round two adds targeted rebuttals with source URLs, not just opinions.
Users submit a blind verdict before evidence, source, and logic scores are revealed.
Every verdict is saved and later backtested against real market prices.
Demo Mode lets judges test the full workflow even when API quota is unavailable.
Codex and GPT-5.6 shaped the full stack, schemas, prompts, tests, and UX decisions.
The goal is not trading automation. The goal is better recorded judgment.